Have you just made a new film, Miss Marsh?
您刚拍完一部新电影吗,Marsh小姐?
Yes, I have.
是的,我刚拍完.
Are you going to make another?
您准备再拍一部吗?
No, I'm not.
不,我不准备拍了.
I'm going to retire.
我准备退休了.
I feel very tired.
我感觉累得很.
I don't want to make another film for a long time.
我很长一段时间内都不想再拍片子了.
Let's buy a newspaper, Liz.
我们买份报纸吧.Liz.
Listen to this!
听这个
Karen Marsh:Sensational News!By our reporter,Alan Jones.
“Karen Marsh：爆炸性新闻!由本报记者Alan Jones报道.
Karen Marsh arrived at London Airport today.
Karen Marsh今天到达伦敦机场.
She was wearing a blue dress and a mink coat.
她穿着一身蓝色的套装和一件貂皮大衣.
She told me she had just made a new film.
她告诉我她刚拍完一部新片子.
she said she was not going to make another.
她说她不准备再拍电影了.
She said she was going to retire.
她说她准备退休.
She told reporters she felt very tired
她告诉记者她感到很疲劳,
and didn't want to make another film for a long time.'
很长一段时间内都不想再拍片子了.”
I wonder why!
我很想知道为什么.